A Finding Aid to the W.G. Constable Papers, 1905-1983, bulk 1920-1976, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Research Files, 1922-1976; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 7.5 Linear feet Box 16-24, OV 28-29
  - Artists, Vedute Painters, 1922-1967; 8.3; Archival Resource Key
    Materials include notes, lists, correspondence, and printed and photographic reference material related to vedute/topographical painters and vedute school followers. Substantial material on Francesco Battaglioli, Luca Carlevaris, Francesco Guardi, Antonio Joli, Samuel Scott, and Francesco Tironi can be found in this subseries.
    - Battaglioli, Francesco, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Battaglioli, Francesco, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bella, Gabriele, 1922-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Borsato, Giuseppe, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Brancaleoni, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Busiri, Giovanni, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15)
      Biographical material, contemporary artists, exhibitions.
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
      On artwork, views of Venice, miscellaneous.
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (notes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
      Architecture.
    - Carlevaris, Luca (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22)
      Fabriche e Vedute.
    - Carlevaris, Luca (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Carlevaris, Luca (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
      Figure sketches, paintings.
    - Carlevaris, Luca (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Cimaroli, Gianbattista, circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Cimaroli, Gianbattista, circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Clerisseau, Charles-Louis, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Costa, Gianfrancesco, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Diziani, Antonio, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Diziani, Gaspari, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Domenichini, Apollonio, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Edwards, Pietro, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Fabris, Jacob, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Fabris, Pietro, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Garola, Pietro Francesco, circa 1950-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Gaspari Family, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Gravenbrock Family, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Griffier, Robert, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Guardi, Francesco (private collections), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Guardi, Francesco (private collections), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Guardi, Francesco (forgeries), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 42)
      Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 5.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, biographical material), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, early works), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, drawings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, drawings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, paintings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Guardi, Francesco (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Guardi, Francesco (photographs of artwork), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci drawings and landscapes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci drawings and landscapes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci drawings and landscapes), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci ruins), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Arch, castle, and Roman ruins.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci ruins), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci ruins), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci ruins), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Venetian buildings and villages. Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 5.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Capricci ruins), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Venetian buildings and villages.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Arsenal, assemblages, and Bacino di San Marco.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Arsenal, assemblages, and Bacino di San Marco. Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 5.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Canals and churches.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 19)
      Fondamenta Nuova and Grand Canal.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 21)
      Lagoon, Papal visit, and Piazza San Marco. Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 5.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 23)
      Lagoon, Papal visit, and Piazza San Marco.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 24)
      Piazzetta, Rialto Bridge, and Riva Degli Schiavone.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 27)
      San Giorgio Aggiore and San Maria Della Dogana.
    - Guardi, Francesco (notes, Venice site specific artworks), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Guardi, Giacomo, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Guardi, Giovanni Antonio, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Jackson, J.B., circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Joli, Antonio (#1), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Joli, Antonio (#2), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Joli, Antonio (#3), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Joli, Antonio (#4), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Marlow, William, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Moretti, Giuseppi, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Navone, Francesco, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Panini, Giovanni, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Patch, Thomas, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Richter, Jan, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Richter, Johann, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Scalvini, Petrus, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Scott, Samuel (notes, biographical material and London), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Scott, Samuel (notes, biographical material and London), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Scott, Samuel (notes, Westminster Bridge), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Scott, Samuel (notes, Westminster Bridge), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Joseph, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Stom, Antonio, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Tironi, Francesco, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Tironi, Francesco, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Valeriani, Giuseppe, circa 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Van Link, Hendrick Frans, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Vanvitelli, Gaspar (notes, Florence, Naples, and Rome), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Vanvitelli, Gaspar (notes, Florence, Naples, and Rome), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Vanvitelli, Gaspar (notes, Venice and drawings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Vanvitelli, Gaspar (notes, Venice and drawings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Zanetti, Antonio, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Topographical Painters, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Topographical Painters, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Vedute Painters, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Vedute Painters, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Vedute Painters, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Notes on Vedute School Followers, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Notes on Vedute School Followers, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Oversize Photographs of Artwork, Guardi, Francesco scanned with Box 19, Folder 42, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Oversize Photographs of Artwork, Guardi, Francesco scanned with Box 20, Folders 10, 15, and 21-22, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Oversize Photographs of Artwork, Moretti, Giuseppi scanned with Box 20, Folder 37, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Museum Conservation, circa 1940-1960; 8.4; Archival Resource Key
    Materials consist of notes, reports, articles, and miscellaneous printed and photographic material regarding techniques relevant to museum conservation and curation.
    - Aquisition Policies, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Canvas Relining, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Cleaning, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Fading, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Framing and Mounting, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Gallery Display and Storage, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Gallery Lighting, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Gallery Lighting, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Painting Inspection, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Painting Techniques, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Pastels, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Research Rooms, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Restoration, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Restoration Panals, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Solvents, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Ventilation Systems, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Oversize Blueprints, Gallery Display and Storage, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 29)
      Oversized material scanned with Box 21, Folder 19.
  - Museums and Galleries, 1930-1965; 8.5; Archival Resource Key
    Materials consist of notes, aquisition reports, memoranda, meeting minutes, and photographs of artwork for museums that Constable worked with in an advisory capacity.
    - Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (photographs of arwork, A-M), 1938-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (photographs of artwork, N-Z), 1938-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa (acquisitions), 1932-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa (reports), 1931-1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa (reports), 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa (duplicate reports), 1931-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, A-C), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, D-H), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, I-L), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, M-P), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, R-S), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, T-U), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Walker Art Center (photographs of artwork, V-Z), circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Watts Gallery, Accounts, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Watts Gallery, Minutes and Reports, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Watts Gallery, Clippings, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Oversize Landscape Diagram, Watts Gallery scanned with Box 21, Folder 46, circa 1958-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 29)
  - Private Collections, 1930-1964; 8.6; Archival Resource Key
    Materials include notes, lists, correspondence, and photographs describing artworks owned by private collectors in North America and Europe, with particular emphasis given to American and British collections. The subseries also includes information on works of art handled through dealers and auction houses.
    - American, New England, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - American, New England, A-E Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American, New England, F-Q Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American, New England, R-Z Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American, California, District of Columiba, Indiana, Michigan, Missouri, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American, Ohio, New York, Pennsylvania, Virginia, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American, Virginia (Mellon, Paul), 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American, Virginia (Mellon, Paul), 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - British, A Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - British, BA Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - British, BE Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - British, BI-BU Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - British, CA-CH Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - British, CL-CU Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - British, DA-DE Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - British, Douglas, R. Langton, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - British, E-F Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - British, G Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - British, HA-HE Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - British, HI-HY Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - British, J-K Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - British, LA-LE Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - British, LO-LU Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - British, Lee, Lord, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - British, M Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - British, N Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - British, O-P Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - British, Q-S Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - British, T Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - British, WA-WI Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - British, Woburn Abbey, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - British, WO-WZ, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Canadian, A-Z Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - European, A-J Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - European, K-Z Miscellaneous, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 35)
      Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 6.
    - Auction House, Christie's, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Auction House, Christie's (slides and negatives), circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Dealers, Agnew's, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Dealers, Goldsmith's Hall, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Reference Resources, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Oversize Catalog, European, A-Z Miscellaneous scanned with Box 22, Folder 35, circa 1930-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Public Collections, circa 1930-1960; 8.7; Archival Resource Key
    Materials include notes, lists, correspondence, and photographs describing artworks owned by public galleries and museums in North America and Europe, with particular emphasis given to American and British institutions.
    - American, California, Colorado, Indiana, Massachusetts, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - American, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Texas, Wisconsin, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - American, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - British, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - British, Westminster Abbey, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - British, Westminster Abbey, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - British, Winchester School, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Canadian, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - European, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - European, circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - European (notebooks), circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - European (notebooks), circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - European (notebooks), circa 1930-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Reference Cards, circa 1940-1960; 8.8; Archival Resource Key
    Materials consist of note cards referencing bibliographic sources related to Constable's research interests, including the Venetian artist Canaletto, private and public art collections, and European schools of art.
    - Artists, Canaletto, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Private and Public Art Collections, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Schools of Art, European, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Schools of Art, Italy, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Schools of Art, circa 1940-1960; 8.9; Archival Resource Key
    Materials include notes, lists, correspondence, and printed and photographic materials related to styles of European art, with particular emphasis given to genres of English, German, Italian, and Scandinavian art.
    - American Contemporary, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Austrian, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Bohemian, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Bohemian, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Dutch, circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - English (reference sources), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - English (medieval), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - English (14th century), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29)
      Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 7.
    - English (15th century), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - English (16th century), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - English (16-19th century), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - English (paintings), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - English (portraits), circa 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 34)